Finding Aid for the Miriam Matthews collection of Los Angeles Newspapers on African Americans, ca. 1948-1985
UCLA Library Special Collections
- L.A. Sentinel. Volumes: XXXI, Aug. 25, 1966 - Dec. 29, 1966.; 16 items.
  - L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XXXI, Issue: No. 52, Dec. 29, 1966.; 36 pages; 4 sections, 15 cents (Box 7)
    Headline: Air Horn Blast Triggers Murder + Rose Float Flops
  - L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XXXI, Issue: No. 37, Sep. 15, 1966.; 44 pages; 4 sections, 15 cents (Box 7)
    Headline: Dope Pair 'Fixed' + Human Relations Units to Act to Avert Local War
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XXXII, June 22, 1967; June 29, 1967; July 6, 1967; July 13, 1967; July 27, 1967; Aug. 3, 1967; Aug. 17, 1967; Aug. 24, 1967; Oct. 12, 1967. (Box 8)
  Issues: No. 25, No.26, No.27, No.28, No.30, No.31, No.33, No.34, No.41
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XXXII; XXXIV, Apr. 11, 1968; Jan. 18, 1968; Jan. 25, 1968; Feb. 22, 1968; Feb. 29, 1968; Apr. 4, 1968; May 16, 1968; May 23, 1968; May 30, 1968; June 6, 1968. (Box 9)
  Issues: No. 15, No.3, No.4, No.8, No.9, No.13, No.20, No.21, No.22, No.23
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XXXII; XXXIV; XXXV, June 20, 1968; July 4, 1968; July 11, 1968; July 18, 1968; July 25, 1968; Aug. 1, 1968; Sep. 5, 1968; Sep. 12, 1968; Dec. 5, 1968; Dec. 26, 1968. (Box 10)
  Issues: No. 25, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 30, No. 31, No. 36, No. 37, No. 49, No. 52
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XXXVI; XXXVII, ; Jan. 2, 1969; Jan. 16, 1969; Jan. 30, 1969; Feb. 20, 1969; Feb. 27, 1969; Mar. 6, 1969; Mar. 13, 1969; Mar. 20, 1969; Mar. 27, 1969; Apr. 3, 1969; Apr. 10, 1969; Apr. 24, 1969; Jan. 29, 1970; Aug. 20, 1970; Sep. 17, 1970; Nov. 19, 1970. (Box 11)
  Issues: No. 1, No.3, No.5, No.8, No.9, No.10, No.11, No.12, No.13, No.14, No.15, No.17, No.5, No.34, No.38, No.47
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XXXVII; XXXVIII; XXXIX, Feb. 18, 1971; Oct. 7, 1971; Oct. 21, 1971; Feb. 3, 1972; Feb. 10, 1972; Feb. 17, 1972; Feb. 24, 1972; Mar. 2, 1972; Mar. 9, 1972; Mar. 16, 1972; Mar. 30, 1972; Apr. 6, 1972; Apr. 13, 1972. (Box 12)
  Issues: No. 7, No. 40, No. 42, No. 5, No. 6, No. 7, No. 8, No. 9, No. 10, No. 11, No. 13, No. 14, No. 15
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XL; XLI, Jan. 4, 1973; Jan. 18, 1973; Jan. 25, 1973; Feb. 1, 1973; Feb. 8, 1973; Feb. 15, 1973; Feb. 22, 1973; Mar. 1, 1973; Mar. 8, 1973; Mar. 15, 1873; Mar. 22, 1973; Mar. 29, 1973; Apr. 5, 1973; Apr. 12, 1973. (Box 13)
  Issues: No. 1, No. 3, No. 4, No. 5, No. 6, No. 7, No. 8, No. 9, No. 10, No. 11, No. 12, No. 13, No. 1, No. 2
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLI, Apr. 19, 1973; May 3, 1973; May 10, 1973; May 17, 1973; May 24, 1973; May 31, 1973; June 7, 1973; June 14, 1973; June 21, 1973; June 28, 1973; July 5, 1973; July 12, 1973; July 19, 1973; July 26, 1973. (Box 14)
  Issues: No. 3, No. 5, No. 6, No. 7, No. 8, No. 9, No. 10, No. 11, No. 12, No. 13, No. 14, No. 15, No. 16, No. 17
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLI, Aug. 2, 1973;; Aug. 9, 1973; Aug. 16, 1973; Aug. 23, 1973; Aug. 30, 1973; Sep. 6, 1973; Sep. 20, 1973; Sep. 27, 1973; Oct. 4, 1973; Oct. 11, 1973; Oct. 18, 1973; Oct. 25, 1973; Nov. 1, 1973; Nov. 15, 1973; Nov. 22, 1973; Nov. 29, 1973; Dec. 6, 1973; Dec. 13, 1973; Dec. 20, 1973.
  Issues: No. 18, No. 19, No. 20, No. 21, No. 22, No. 23, No. 25, No. 26, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 30, No. 31, No. 33, No. 34, No. 35, No. 36, No. 37, No. 38
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLI; XLII, Jan. 3, 1974;; Jan. 17, 1974; Jan. 24, 1974; Jan. 31, 1974; Feb. 14, 1974; Feb. 21, 1974; Feb. 28, 1974; Mar. 7, 1974; Mar. 14, 1974; Mar. 21, 1974; Apr. 11, 1974; Apr. 18, 1974; May 2, 1974; May 9, 1974; May 16, 1974; May 23, 1974; June 13, 1974; June 27, 1974; July 4, 1974; Aug. 1, 1974; Aug. 8, 1974. (Box 16)
  Issues: No. 40, No. 42, No. 43, No. 44, No. 46, No. 47, No. 48, No. 49, No. 50, No. 51, No. 2, No. 3, No. 5, No. 6, No. 7, No. 8, No. 11, No. 13, No. 18, No. 18(2)
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLII, Aug. 15, 1974; Aug. 22, 1974; Aug. 29, 1974; Sep. 5, 1974; Sep. 12, 1974; Sep. 26, 1974; Oct. 3, 1974; Oct. 10, 1974; Oct. 17, 1974; Oct. 31, 1974; Nov. 7, 1974; Nov. 14, 1974; Nov. 28, 1974; Dec. 5, 1974; Dec. 12, 1974. (Box 17)
  Issues: No. 20, No. 21, No. 22, No. 23, No. 24, No. 26, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 31, No. 32, No. 33, No. 35, No. 36, No. 37
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLII; XLIII, Jan. 2, 1975; Jan. 9, 1975; Jan. 16, 1975; Jan. 30, 1975; Feb. 13, 1975; Feb. 20, 1975; Feb. 27, 1975; Mar. 13, 1975; Mar. 20, 1975; Mar. 27, 1975; Apr. 3, 1975; Apr. 17, 1974; Apr. 24, 1975; Apr. 3, 1975; Apr. 17, 1975; Apr. 24, 1975; May 1, 1975; May 8, 1975; May 15, 1975; May 22, 1975. (Box 18)
  Issues: No. 40, No. 41, No. 42, No. 44, No. 46, No. 47, No. 48, No. 50, No. 51, No. 52, No. 1, No. 3, No. 3, No. 4, No. 5, No. 6, No. 7, No. 8
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XIIII; XLIII, May 29, 1975; June 5, 1975; June 12, 1975; June 19, 1975; June 26, 1975; July 3, 1975; July 10, 1975; July 17, 1975; July 24, 1975; Aug. 2, 1975; Aug. 14, 1975; Aug. 21, 1975; Aug. 28, 1975; Sep. 2, 1975; Nov. 13, 1975. (Box 19)
  Issues: No. 9, No. 10, No. 11, No. 12, No. 13, No. 14, No. 15, No. 16, No. 17, No. 19, No. 20, No. 21, No. 22, No. 27, No. 33
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLIV, Apr. 1, 1976, Apr. 8, 1975; Apr. 15, 1975; Apr. 29, 1975; May 6, 1975; May 13, 1975; May 20, 1975; June 3, 1975; June 10, 1975; June 17, 1975; June 24, 1975; July 8, 1975; July 15, 1975; July 22, 1975. (Box 20)
  Issues: No. 2, No. 3, No. 4, No. 6, No. 7, No. 8, No. 9, No. 10, No. 11, No. 12, No. 14, No. 15, No. 16, No. 17
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLIV, July 29, 1976; Aug. 5, 1976; Aug. 12, 1976; Aug. 19, 1976; Aug. 26, 1976; Sep. 2, 1976; Sep. 9, 1976; Sep. 16, 1976; Sep. 23, 1976; Sep. 30, 1976; Oct. 7, 1976; Oct. 14, 1976; Oct. 21, 1976; Oct. 28, 1976; Nov. 4, 1976; Nov. 11, 1976; Dec. 2, 1976; Dec. 9, 1976; Dec. 16, 1976; Dec. 23, 1976; Dec. 30, 1976.. (Box 21)
  Issues: No. 18, No. 19, No. 20, No. 21, No. 22, No. 23, No. 24, No. 25, No. 26, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 30, No. 31, No. 32, No. 33, No. 36, No. 37, No. 38, No. 39, No. 40
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLIV; XLI, Jan. 6, 1977; Jan. 13, 1977; Jan. 20, 1977; Jan. 27, 1977; Feb. 3, 1977; Feb. 10, 1977; Feb. 17, 1977; Feb. 24, 1977; Mar. 3, 1977; Mar. 10, 1977; Mar. 17, 1977; Mar. 24, 1977; Apr. 7, 1977; Apr. 14, 1977; Apr. 21, 1977; Apr. 28, 1977. (Box 22)
  Issues: No. 41, No. 42, No. 43, No. 44, No. 45, No. 46, No. 47, No. 48, No. 49, No. 50, No. 51, No. 52, No. 1, No. 3, No. 4, No. 5
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLI, May 5, 1977; May 12, 1977; May 19, 1977; May 26, 1977; June 2, 1977; June 9, 1977; June 16, 1977; June 23, 1977; June 30, 1977; July 7, 1977; July 14, 1977; July 28, 1977.; L.A. Sentinel forgot to change issue for issue 19. (Box 23)
  Issues: No. 6, No. 7, No. 8, No. 9, No. 10, No. 11, No. 12, No. 13, No. 14, No. 15, No. 16, No. 17, No. 18, No. 19, No. 21
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLI; XLV, Sep. 1, 1977; Sep. 8, 1977; Sep. 15, 1977; Sep. 22, 1977; Sep. 29, 1977; Oct. 6, 1977; Oct. 13, 1977; Oct. 20, 1977; Oct. 27, 1977; Nov. 3, 1977; Nov. 10, 1977; Dec. 8, 1977; Dec. 15, 1977; Dec. 22, 1977; Dec. 29, 1977. (Box 24)
  Issues: No. 22, No. 23, No. 24, No. 25, No. 26, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 30, No. 31, No. 32, No. 36, No. 37, No. 38, No. 39
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLV; XLVI, Jan. 5, 1978; Jan. 12, 1978; Jan 19, 1978; Jan. 26, 1978; Feb. 2, 1978; Feb. 9, 1978; Feb.16, 1978; Feb. 23, 1978; Mar. 6, 1978; Mar. 13, 1978; Mar. 20, 1978; Mar. 27, 1978; Apr. 4, 1978. (Box 25)
  Issues: No. 37, No. 38, No. 42, No. 43, No. 44, No. 45, No. 46, No. 47, No. 49, No. 50, No. 51, No. 15, No. 26, No. 45, No. 5, No. 6
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVI; XLIV, May 11, 1978; June 1, 1978; June 15, 1978; July 6, 1978; July 13, 1978; 20, 1978; Aug. 3, 1978; Aug. 10, 1978; Aug. 17, 1978; Aug. 31, 1978; Sep. 7, 1978; Sep.21, 1978; Sep. 28, 1978; Sep. 5, 1978; Sep. 12, 1978; Nov. 30, 1978; Dec. 7, 1978; Dec. 14, 1978; Dec. 21, 1978. (Box 26)
  Issues: No. 7, No. 10, No. 12, No. 15, No. 16, No. 17, No. 19, No. 20, No. 21, No. 23, No. 24, No. 26, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 36, No. 37, No. 38, No. 39
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLIV; XLV, Jan. 4, 1979; Jan. 11, 1979; Jan. 18, 1979; Jan. 25, 1979; Jan. 8, 1979; Jan. 22, 1979; Jan 1, 1979; Jan 8, 1979; Jan 15, 1979; Jan 22, 1979; Jan 29, 1979; Feb. 5, 1979; Feb. 9, 1979; Feb. 26, 1979.; 14 Items (Box 27)
  Issues: No. 41, No. 42, No. 43, No. 44, No. 46, No. 48, No. 49, No. 50, No. 51, No. 52, No. 1, No. 2, No. 4, No. 5
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLV, May 3, 1979; May 10, 1979; May 17, 1979; May 24, 1979; June 7, 1979; June 14, 1979; June 21, 1979; June 28, 1979; July 19, 1979; July 26, 1979; Aug. 2, 1979; Aug. 9, 1979; Aug. 23, 1979; Aug. 30, 1979; Sep. 6, 1979; Sep. 13, 1979.; 16 Items (Box 28)
  Issues: No. 6, No. 7, No. 8, No. 9, No. 11, No. 12, No. 13, No. 14, No. 17, No. 18, No. 19, No. 20, No. 22, No. 23, No. 24, No. 25
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLV, Sep. 20, 1979; Sep. 27, 1979; Oct. 4, 1979; Oct. 11, 1979; Oct. 18, 1979; Oct. 25, 1979; Nov. 1, 1979; Nov. 8, 1979; Nov. 15, 1979; Nov. 22, 1979; Nov. 29, 1979; Dec. 6, 1979; Dec. 13, 1979; Dec. 20, 1979; Dec. 27, 1979.; 15 Items (Box 29)
  Issues: No. 26, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 30, No. 31, No. 32, No. 33, No. 34, No. 35, No. 36, No. 37, No. 38, No. 38(2), No. 39
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVI, Aug. 7, 1980; Aug. 14, 1980; Aug. 21, 1980; Aug. 28, 1980; Sep. 4, 1980; Sep. 11, 1980; Sep. 18, 1980; Oct. 2, 1980; Oct. 9, 1980; Oct. 16, 1980; Oct. 23, 1980; Oct. 30, 1980; Nov. 6, 1980; Nov. 13, 1980; Nov. 20, 1980; Nov. 27, 1980; Dec. 4, 1980; Dec. 11, 1980; Dec. 18, 1980; Dec. 25, 1980.; 20 Items
  Issues: No. 17, No. 18, No. 19, No. 20, No. 21, No. 22, No. 23, No. 25, No. 25(2),No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 30, No. 31, No. 32, No. 33, No. 34, No. 35, No. 36, No. 37
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVI; XLVII, Jan. 1, 1981; Jan 8, 1981; Jan. 15, 1981; Jan. 22, 1981; Jan. 29, 1981; Feb. 12, 1981; Feb. 19, 1981; Feb. 26, 1981; Mar. 5, 1981; Mar. 12, 1981; Mar. 19, 1981; Mar. 26, 1981; Apr. 2, 1981; Apr. 9, 1981; Apr. 16, 1981. (Box 31)
  Issues: No. 38, No. 39, No. 40, No. 41, No. 43, No. 44, No. 45, No. 9(46), No. 47, No. 48, No. 49, No. 50, No. 51, No. 52, No. 1
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVII, Apr. 23, 1981; Apr. 30, 1981; May 7, 1981; May, 14, 1981; June 11, 1981; June 18, 1981; June 25, 1981; July 2, 1981; July 9, 1981; July 16, 1981; July 23, 1981; July 30, 1981; Aug. 6, 1981; Aug. 13, 1981; Aug. 20, 1981; Aug. 27, 1981; Sep. 3, 1981. (Box 32)
  Issues: No. 2, No. 3, No. 4, No. 5, No. 9, No. 10, No. 11, No. 12, No. 13, No. 14, No. 16, No. 17, No. 18, No. 19, No. 20
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVII, Sep. 10, 1981; Sep. 17, 1982; Sep. 24, 1981; Oct. 8, 1981; Oct. 16; 1981; Nov. 5, 1981; Nov. 12, 1981; Nov. 19, 1981; Nov. 26, 1981; Dec. 3, 1981; Dec. 10, 1981; Dec. 17, 1981; Dec. 24, 1981; Dec. 31, 1981. (Box 33)
  Issues: No. 22, No. 23, No. 24, No. 26, No. 27, No. 30, No. 31, No. 32, No. 33, No. 34, No. 35, No. 36, No. 37, No. 38
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVII, Jan. 7, 1982; Jan. 14, 1982; Jan. 21, 1982; Feb. 4, 1982 Feb. 11, 1982; Feb. 18, 1982; Feb. 25, 1982; Mar. 4, 1982; Mar. 11, 1982; Mar. 18, 1982; Mar. 25, 1982, Apr. 1, 1982; Apr. 8, 1982; Apr. 15, 1982.; Issue No. 43 (Feb. 18, 1982) Miriam Matthews Receives Titus Alexander Award (Box 34)
  Issues: No. 39, No. 40, No. 41, No. 41(2), No. 42, No. 43, No. 44, No. 45, No. 46, No. 47, No. 48, No. 49, No. 50, No. 51
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVII; XLVIII, Apr. 22, 1982; Apr. 29, 1982; May 6, 1982; May 13, 1982; May 20, 1982; May 27, 1982; June 3, 1982; June 10, 1982; June 17, 1982; June 24, 1982; July 1, 1982; July 8, 1982; July 15, 1982; July 22, 1982; July 29, 1982. (Box 35)
  Issues: No. 52, No. 1, No. 2, No. 3, No. 4, No. 5, No. 6, No. 7, No. 8, No. 9, No. 10, No. 11, No. 12, No. 13, No. 14
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVIII, Aug. 5, 1982; Aug. 12, 1982; Aug. 19, 1982; Aug. 26, 1982; Sep. 2, 1982; Sep. 9, 1982; Sep. 16, 1982; Sep. 23, 1982; Sep. 30, 1982; Oct. 7, 1982; Oct. 14, 1982; Oct. 21, 1982; Oct. 28, 1982; Nov. 4, 1982; Nov. 11, 1982; Dec. 16, 1982. (Box 36)
  Issues: No. 15, No. 16, No. 17, No. 18, No. 19, No. 20, No. 21, No. 22, No. 23, No. 24, No. 25, No. 26, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 34
- L.A. Sentinel. Volume: XLVII; XLIX; L, Feb. 24, 1983; July 7, 1983, Apr. 12, 1984; Apr. 19, 1984; Sep. 27,1984; Oct. 4, 1984; Oct. 11, 1984; Oct. 18, 1984; Oct. 25, 1984; Nov. 1, 1984; Nov. 8, 1984; Nov. 15, 1984; Nov. 22, 1984; Nov. 29, 1984, Dec. 6, 1984; Dec. 13, 1984; Dec. 20, 1984; Dec. 27, 1984; Feb. 21, 1985; Mar. 7, 1985; Mar. 14, 1985. (Box 37)
  Issues: No. 44, No. 11, No. 51, No. 52, No. 23, No. 24, No. 2, No. 26, No. 27, No. 28, No. 29, No. 30, No. 31, No. 32, No. 33, No. 34, No. 35, No. 36, No. 44, No. 46, No. 47
- Los Angeles Sentinel., Special Issue Black Progress in So Cal XXXVII, Thursday May 20, 1971 (two copies); Special Issue Black Progress in So Cal XXXVIII, Thursday May 27, 1971 (two copies); Special Edition Sentinel Publisher Dies XLII, Thursday June 20, 1974; Special Edition Sentiel's 50 XLVIII, Thursday April 14, 1983 (three copies). (Box 38)
  Issues: No. 20, No. 21, No. 12, No. 51
- LA Times, Muhammad Speaks, LA City Press, Tribune News Wave, California Eagle. Volume:, LA Times: XCIII, Friday May 24, 1974; Sunday June 30, 1974 (partial); Friday May 24, 1974 (partial); Sunday May 5, 1974 Muhammad Speaks: 13, May 31, 1974 LA City Press: 43, Wednesday Aug. 27, 1980 (2 pages) Tribune News Wave: 54, Thursday Feb. 21, 1980 (2 pages); 54, Thursday Feb. 7, 1980 (2 pages) California Eagle: Thursday January 7, 1965 (partial); LXXXIV, Thursday Dec. 5, 1963.; No issue numbers for LA Times; No issue number for partial California Eagle (Box 39)
  Issues: Muhammad Speaks: No. 38; LA City Press: No. 35; Tibune News Wave: No. 44, No. 42, No. 5, No. 24, No. 7, No. 8, No. 47, No. 31, No. 48, No. 22, No. 30, No. 25, No. 33, No. 46, No. 27, N. 14, No. 41, No. 32; California Eagle: No. 38
- California Eagle., Thursday April 10, 1958 (partial); Thursday April 24, 1958 (partial); Thursday May 8, 1958 (partial); Thursday February 18, 1960 (partial); Thursday February 25, 1960 (partial); Thursday July 28, 1960 (partial); Thursday September 29, 1960 (partial); Thursday December 15, 1960 (partial); Thursday August 24, 1961 (partial); Thursday October 5, 1961 (partial); Thursday October 24, 1961, Thursday November 16, 1961 (partial); Thursday November 23, 1961 (partial); Thursday December 7, 1961 (partial); Thursday February 8, 1962(partial); Thursday February 22, 1962 (partial); Thursday March 1, 1962 (partial); Thursday March 8, 1962 (partial); Thursday August 8, 1963 (partial); Thursday October 24, 1963 (partial); Thursday October 31, 1963 (partial); Thursday November 21, 1963 (partial); Thursday December 12, 1963 (partial); Thursday January 23, 1964 (partial); Thursday January 30, 1964 (partial); Thursday February 6, 1964 (partial); Thursday February 13, 1964 (partial); Thursday February 27, 1964 (partial); Thursday March 5, 1964 (partial); Thursday March 19, 1964 (partial); Thursday April 16, 1964 (partial); Thursday May 28, 1964 (partial); Thursday June 4 1964 (partial); Thursday August 20, 1964.; Random pages from California Eagle (Box 40)
  Issues: Vol. LXXVIII- Nos. 4, 6, 8; Vol. LXXIX- Nos. 49, 50; Vol. LXXX- Nos. 19,28, 39; Vol. LXXXI- Nos. 23, 29, 32, 35, 36, 38, 47, 49, 50, 51; Vol. LXXXIV- Nos. ?, 32, 33, 36, 39, 45, 46, 47, 48, 50, 51 (copy 1 of 2), 51 (copy 2 of 2); Vol. LXXXV- Nos. 1, 5, 11, 12, 23
- Los Angeles Tribune., Friday February28, 1958 (partial); Friday June 27, 1958 (partial); Friday July 25, 1958 (partial); Friday August 1, 1958 (partial); Friday August 29, 1958 (partial); Friday September 5, 1958 (partial); Friday September 12. 1958 (partial); Friday September 19, 1958 (partial); Friday September 26, 1958 (partial); Friday October 3, 1958 (partial); Friday October 10, 1958 (partial); Friday October 17, 1958 (partial); Friday October 31, 1984 (partial); Friday November 7, 1958 (partial); Friday November 14, 1958 (partial); Friday November 21, 1958 (partial); Friday December 5, 1958 (partial); Friday December 26, 1958 (partial); Friday January 2, 1959 (partial); Friday January 9, 1959 (partial); Friday January 23, 1959 (partial); Friday January 30, 1959 (partial); Friday February 6, 1959 (partial); Friday February 13, 1959 (partial); Friday March 20, 1959 (partial); Friday April 3, 1959 (partial); Friday April 10, 1959 (partial); Friday April 24, 1959 (partial); Friday May 1, 1959 (partial); Friday May 29, 1959 (partial); Friday June 5, 1959 (partial); Friday June 12, 1959 (partial); Friday June 26, 1959 (partial); Friday July 3, 1959 (partial); Friday July 17, 1959 (partial); Friday July 24, 1959 (partial); Friday July 31, 1959 (partial); Friday August 7, 1959 (partial); Friday February 26, 1950 (partial); Friday March 11, 1960 (partial); Friday March 18, 1960 (partial); Friday March 25, 1960 (partial); Friday April 8, 1960 (partial); Friday April 15, 1960 (partial). (Box 41)
  Issues: Vol. 18- Nos. 3, 20, 24, 25, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35 (copy 1 of 2), 35 (copy 2 of 2), 38, 39, 40, 41, 43, 46, 47, 48, 50, 51, 52; Vol. 19- Nos. 1, 6, 8, 9, 11, 12 (copy 1 of 2), 12 (copy 2 of 2), ?, 17, 18, 20, 21, 23, 24, ?, 26; Vol. 20- Nos. 3, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10,
- Los Angeles Tribune., Saturday June 19, 1948 (partial); Saturday August 6, 1949 (partial); Saturday August 20, 1949 (partial); Saturday August 27, 1949 (partial); Friday November 4, 1955 (partial); Friday November 11, 1955 (partial); Friday November 18, 1955 (partial); Friday July 27, 1956 (partial); Friday August 3, 1956 (partial); Wednesday November 27, 1957 (partial); Friday February 21, 1958 (partial); Friday March 28, 1958 (partial); Friday April 4, 1958 (partial); Friday April 11, 1958 (partial); Friday April 18, 1958 (partial); Friday April 25, 1958 (partial); Friday May 2, 1958 (partial); Friday May 9, 1958 (partial); Friday May 16, 1958 (partial); Friday May 23, 1958 (partial); Friday May 30, 1958 (partial); Friday June 6, 1958 (partial); Friday June 13, 1958 (partial); Friday June 20, 1958 (partial); Friday July 4, 1958 (partial); Friday July 11, 1958 (partial); Friday July 18, 1958 (partial); Friday August 8, 1958 (partial); Friday December 12, 1958 (partial); Friday August 14, 1959 (partial); Friday September 11, 1959 (partial); Friday October 2, 1959 (partial); Friday October 16, 1959 (partial); Friday October 23, 1959 (partial); Friday October 30, 1959 (partial); Friday November 6, 1959 (partial); Friday November 13, 1959 (partial); Friday November 20, 1959 (partial); Friday December 11, 1959 (partial); Friday December 25, 1959 (partial); Friday January 1, 1960 (partial); Friday January 8, 1960 (partial); Friday January 15, 1960 (partial); Friday January 22, 1960 (partial); Friday January 29, 1960 (partial); Friday February 5, 1960.; The second Vol. 9- No. 27 is incorrectly labeled and would therefore be No. 28 (Box 42)
  Issues: Vol. 8- No. 19; ?; Vol. 9- No. 27; Vol. 9- No. 27; Vol. 15- Nos. 38, 39, 40; Vol. 16- Nos. 24, 25; Vol. 17- No. 42; Vol. 18- Nos. 2, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 21, 22, 23, 26, 44; Vol. 19- Nos. 27, 31, 34, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 44, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52